[Music: ‘He’s a Black Flame Dragon’ theme song]
[Tense sound effect]
[dark music]
(Juyeon) Are you crazy?
[Sound of car door closing]
How can I believe you?
Aren't you leaving? They said it was urgent
Damn it
(Edit) For...
[Exciting music]
You...
Huh?
[Scream of Crystal]
Unlucky from the start
You crazy pervert!
(Juyeon) You must be the pervert
I stole it and I got hurt
- (Edited) You...
- (Main role) Team leader Baek Soo-jeong
Is trespassing your hobby?
(Edited) How do you do that...
I said the name was nasty right from the start.
(Edited) So...
The general manager...
[Interesting music]
Are you the general manager?
(Juyeon) Yes, I’m not some crazy pervert.
general manager
I've seen this somewhere before
I'm sure
[Awkward laughter]
How...
No, how did this happen...
It must be a bad relationship.
(Juyeon) It’s not fate
[Sharp sound effect]
[Crackling sound effect]
[humorous music]
That, Director
(Edited) I thought I was the head of the department.
What I said without knowing
I literally thought he was the head of the department.
Because I said these things without knowing
- So the general manager...
- (Juyeon) Let’s forget everything.
Yes, thank you if you forget everything...
[ding sound effect]
This easy?
[Sharp sound effect]
- Do you not like it?
- ok
Forget Team Leader Baek Soo-jeong instead of (Juyeon)
You and me
We've never met outside of work.
I didn't see anything just before.
Is it possible?
[Nodding sound effect]
- It is possible
- Let's watch.
Go out and try
[Sound of door opening and closing]
[hits the desk]
[Music that heightens tension]
[Juyeon sighs]
[Siren sound effect]
I can't forget, it was so intense
(Juyeon) Originally, it seemed like the car was on the verge of being scrapped.
I'll pay the repair cost
contact my lawyer
(Edited) Because being a scoundrel and a fool isn’t enough
Even the dragon tattoo...
That's my general manager?
Oh, even though that guy is that guy
Does this make sense?
(Hajin) You often say that when you see Inso, right?
Oh, that's right, I saw it in a webtoon recently too?
So it's a novel and a cartoon.
Ah, I really wanted to do well this time.
If you see that I want to forget everything
Aren’t you a person with a distinction between construction and construction?
(Edited) I don’t feel good
We both say let's forget it all
It didn't seem like that would be the case.
That bastard, there's an end to it, it's clear
(Hajin) You’ll see when you see it.
Don't worry in advance, just eat this first
It was spicy to suit your taste, very spicy.
[lively music]
Looks delicious
[Satisfied moan]
Sharp things are perfect to relieve stress.
[light laughter]
Let's forget everything
When I got off work
What are you thinking about, Chief of Staff?
(Edited) Oh, what should I do with my car repair costs?
(Hajin) Can you see the scratches?
While I'm at it, just pick up a new car
A girl who goes to a department store
You just save money without spending it?
Hmm, the remaining debt plus my dad’s retirement funds.
If I think about it, I need to save more, it's far away.
(Hajin) Anyway, she’s a very dutiful daughter.
You too are a dutiful daughter.
Now you're an unfilial daughter, you're divorced
I made my older sister an unfilial daughter.
Let's kill that bastard too
(Sujeong) Ah, it’s so delicious.
Why are there no customers?
Is it a location issue?
Would you like to promote it to Inbyeol?
farewell?
(Hajin) Ah...
Is this the pain of creation?
[Hajin sighs]
(Hajin) Once you come here, you will never forget it.
Alcohol was love
(Juyeon) I was so busy that I was late in saying hello.
It's an accompaniment.
As Head of Strategic Planning Division
My goal is clear
Yongseong Department Store’s sales doubled
I'm going to double it.
Don't worry too much
I draw the big picture anyway
You just have to be good at coloring
and
Here, Team Leader Baek
Are you saying you're very good at your job?
[light laughter]
thank you
But there was a very funny nickname, right?
Is the general manager a killer?
[Interesting music]
(Juyeon) Let’s make it clear in advance.
I am different from previous general managers
If we fight, I win
You're the one who loses
Leaving the company
I will become team leader Baek.
[Knocking sound]
yes
(In-kyung) It was a very strong first greeting.
(Juyeon) That should be enough
I can't think of anything else.
(Inkyung) Sales doubled
You did that to make me think only about my goals, right?
yes, that's right
The espresso I drink here every day
-Thank you...
- (In-kyung) It’s a triple shot.
- Yes?
- (In-kyung) Getting ready for work
I think you were tired
specially prepared
Try it
Well, that's perfect.
[Sound of putting down glass]
Go try it
[Sound of door opening]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Sound of door closing]
[Clears cough]
[Exciting music]
(Juyeon) Things like this should be legislated
So that I can't drink it
[Painful elasticity]
[Junsu’s sigh]
(Junsu) Ah, the rumor is that the head of the department is the killer.
I guess it's spread too much
They keep me in check as soon as I arrive.
(Nana) That’s right
(Junsu) Ah, when I greeted you yesterday
Was the atmosphere okay?
[Sound of truck passing]
Yes?
(Junsu) Yesterday, I went to the headquarters manager’s office.
You said hello
Was the atmosphere okay at that time?
Yeah, well...
[light music]
(Edited) Huh?
[Scream of Crystal]
Crazy idiot pervert
(Junsu) Oh, it’s okay
Well, just because of rumors
Because that's what you're saying
You just have to do better from now on, from now on
Right?
Well... the team leader is a bit...
I think it would be good if you are good at flattery.
- Flattering?
- (Nana) Huh?
Isn’t that the general manager over there?
(Sujeong) Well, let’s go in first, I’m sorry.
(Nana) Ah...
[Junsu’s muttering]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Sound of swallowing]
(Edited) Would you like to eat that?
[Interesting music]
Ah, I guess you really like sweet things.
I like it too
Do I look like the kind of person who would do that?
yes?
Here, please give me espresso
with triple shot
I only drink espresso
[Card recognition sound]
(Edited) I meant to buy it for you.
Why is Baek Soo-jeong buying mine?
(Edited) I have a discount coupon here.
Because it's your first time here
Flattery is a request
That cheesy
[Humorous sound effects]
[Juyeon’s painful moans]
[Thumping sound effect]
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Sparkling sound effect]
[Sound effect heightens tension]
[upbeat music]
[Juyeon’s surprised moan]
[Exciting music]
Let go, I come first.
Adults must give in
If it's a child, be polite.
I really want this
That's right, I can't get it even through overseas direct purchase.
Hard to find no matter how much money you pay
Because it's a special edition
(Juyeon) It’s all on the floor.
If you don't want to have it
Heh, your insight is appreciated.
But I must have it too
Heh, wow, it’s pretty good, isn’t it?
Mom, this guy is weird!
(Child) Where did mom go?
[Swooshing sound effect]
[Humorous sound effects]
Huh? Director
[light music]
Ah, why are we here...
(Juyeon) What is Baek Soo-jeong?
Are you going to step on my back?
no
I have something to buy
(Edited) Oh, will you buy that, Director?
Oh, I guess you like toys.
[ding sound effect]
This isn't just a toy!
[Humorous sound effects]
[flashing sound effect]
[humorous music]
This kid wanted it so much
(Juyeon) It’s precious.
I'm buying it because you seem so desperate.
You are so kinder than I thought.
(Sujeong) It would be nice to receive a gift
No, this guy...
Just go on your way
(Juyeon) This is useless attention, I refuse.
yes
[Swooshing sound effect]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Fighting sound effect]
[popping sound effect]
goodbye
[Receipt printing sound]
[Sound of kissing]
[Exciting music]
(Juyeon) It’s ridiculous.
It has been completely hidden until now.
my real self
That’s three times for one person
Almost getting caught?
She's dangerous.
At this rate, my social persona
I'll get damaged
[Siren sound effect]
(In-kyung) Removal?
[Interesting music]
Team leader Baek Soo-jeong?
yes
(In-kyung) The story about the general manager’s killer
It was said in the interest of cracking down on discipline.
Well, in the process of resigning from headquarters,
Although there was some commotion
- It wasn’t Team Leader Baek’s fault.
- I did.
- But why?
- This is the result of observation.
Team leader Baek Soo-jeong
It's too dangerous
Strange?
He seemed like a person the general manager would like?
Absolutely not
[Punching the desk] I can't believe my judgment
Are you in doubt?
Because of my personal reasons or feelings
Do you think they want to fire Team Leader Baek?
Is that possible?
There is no such thing as privacy
Everything is centered on the company’s work and performance.
That you are a person who thinks and acts
I know best, right?
[pounds the desk] Yes, you know best.
(In-kyung) Of course
So how do you plan on handling it?
If you just cut it, it's unfair dismissal.
Team leader Baek won’t just sit still either.
There is no such thing in Yongseong.
I have to let it go out on my own feet.
[Devil's Laughing Sound Effect]
[upbeat music]
(Main lead) Yongseong Department Store’s entry into the South American market is
How is it going?
(Edited) After completing the field survey,
We are currently selecting a brand to enter the store.
[Spanish]
(main role)
[Korean] There is a saying like this
[Spanish]
[Upbeat music-continued]
[Korean] Preparing to jump into the sea
I'm sure it's done
[Clears cough]
[Sound of flipping documents]
(Joyeon) What is your market share in South America?
It's 8.74573%, the goal is 14%
Is this a possible goal?
When actively attacking
It is possible within 3 years.
Hmm, easier said than done.
Because it’s not difficult.
I'm overconfident
Is this your style of conceit?
Everyone talks just about words.
I will prove it with the results
(In-kyung) Team Leader Baek is really good at his job.
Preparation is thorough
(Juyeon) Does that matter now?
It's just a target for removal.
[Sound of clenched fist]
[Sound of toilet flushing]
[Sound of door closing]
(Hyeju) Baek Soo-jeong answered well.
It's a compliment, right?
thank you
(Hyeju) Just look at it
I was itching to take a picture of you.
I'm going to overcome it again and again.
The meeting isn't a fight between kids.
I was just answering a question?
(Edited) If it still felt like you won
That's a relief
Because I don't want to lose
(Hyeju) Yes
You don't discriminate between people
The attitude of behaving like a dog fairly
That's one thing I admit
What together?
Then like you
Is it human that you can't tell the difference?
[dark music]
(Hyeju) Hey, take away the poison around your eyes.
Don’t your eyes hurt?
How can a girl be like that?
Are you tough and tough?
Because of kids like you
Women get criticized for being strong.
(Edited) Senior
Don't spit any shit just because it's a toilet.
Please cover your words
- What?
- (Edited) You are a senior at the company.
What do you see from the outside?
[laughter]
I'm worried that I'll get cut off
I told him something, and he was crazy.
(Sujeong) We worked hard to get here.
Senior gave up on marriage
I ended up here because I behaved like a dog.
So just...
Can’t we all get along?
Cursing like people who swear at us?
If this is something you're really worried about, I'd appreciate it.
If I had gone out on my own, I would have gone out.
You won't get cut off or anything like that.
Because my pride won't allow it
yes
No matter how you leave, make sure to call me at the farewell party.
[sigh]
What day is it really today?
[Elevator arrival sound]
(Nana) Oh, hello?
(Shinwon) It’s me, Nana.
I saw it at our new employee welcoming party.
Is this your first time seeing it?
How is this company worth working for?
Ah, ah, yes
(Shinwon) Yes, I’m glad.
Well, how can I get my name...
It's pretty, right?
[lively music]
Yes?
Nana's name is pretty, so it's hard to forget, right?
[Nana’s embarrassed laughter]
(Shinwon) By any chance
Do you have time now?
If it’s okay, I’d like to have a cup of coffee.
I also have some questions
Me, me?
(Shinwon) Yes
yes, good
I have a lot of time
[Nana’s laughter]
(Juyeon) What happened to what I asked you to investigate?
(Shinwon) Ah, well, people around me keep saying
I've been listening to the story, but nothing special happened?
Ah, but do I have to continue with this?
I feel like I'm doing something bad for no reason
I feel bad
Even bad things are work, work hard
But with Director Kwon
Why are you doing this to me?
(Shinwon) Why do you need my help?
i am now
[nervous music]
This is not the time to choose between means and methods.
[Devil's Laughing Sound Effect]
[Employee moans in surprise]
I'm sorry, it's okay, I'm sorry
Why, what's going on?
Why are you sorry?
(Employee) Ah...
thank you
Oh, maybe I
[Embarrassed laughter]
Do you have a girlfriend?
(Shinwon) Ah...
yes
- It'll be there soon, yes.
- (Employee) Oh, yes.
sorry
- Have a good time
- (Identity) Yes
Um...
hmm?
What, what did you talk about with that woman?
Are you here?
Are you hungry? What should I eat?
What did you talk about?
(Shinwon) Uh...
- That's...
- You picked my number again, right?
Of course I refused.
He also said his girlfriend would be coming soon.
Did you smile again?
Were you kind?
Ugh, I just followed social etiquette.
You are too polite.
[Sighing] I’m annoyed.
I won't come here again
Okay, then
(Shinwon) It’ll be even better next time
I'll take you somewhere nice, girl.
So what should I eat?
Because the new general manager has arrived
Let's try our best again!
(together) salty
[Sound of clinking glasses]
Isn’t this a farewell party?
What does that mean?
(Junsu) No, during today’s meeting
I heard that the head of the department openly criticized the team leader?
But the team leader
He didn't say a word there.
No, it was filmed a lot.
There are already rumors
- (Junsu) So
- (Edited) I...
I said let's forget everything and thought there would be an end to it.
Oh, it's okay.
It was filmed not once or twice
don't worry too much
No, it's different this time.
What's different?
Don't you know?
(Junsu) No, no, don’t you know about that rumor?
yes? W-what rumor?
[Door bell sounds]
[Interesting music]
[humorous music]
There's nothing to welcome you like this
How do we get here...
Are you saying you're having a dinner party?
Isn't this my welcome dinner party?
Ah, something like that welcome dinner.
You said you didn't need it...
(Edit) That's right!
Director welcome dinner
This was the dinner party.
[Awkward laughter]
[Junsu’s awkward laughter]
(Nana) Surprise...
I am willing to accept it out of sincerity.
(Juyeon) What are you all doing when you’re not sitting down?
burdensomely
[Sujeong’s awkward laughter]
There seems to be too much scaffolding.
[Embarrassed laughter]
Would you like a drink?
I will pour it for you.
[Interesting music]
Soo-jeong Baek, don’t you drink?
I should drink it too, of course.
[Sound of putting down a bottle]
[Sound of pouring soju]
[Sound of putting down glass]
[Refreshing elasticity of crystals]
[Sound of pouring soju]
Please give me a bottle of soju here.
Two bottles, please!
[Sound of pouring soju]
[Sujeong’s heavy sigh]
(Nana) Ah, how can you two drink so much?
My stomach is pounding
I thought it would be long
I guess I have to get off work now.
(Junsu) Oh, wait a minute, you’re just leaving?
What is the manager doing?
No need to worry
I'm drunk because of the manager
I've never seen it before
[light music]
(In-kyung) He is a very thorough person.
So, whoever wants to go, let's go.
Oh, I also got drunk, team leader.
I've never seen it before...
Go, go
I can really go, really?
[sigh]
Why, why, why, is it hard?
Do you want to stop?
(Edited) I’m completely fine, right?
Are you having a hard time, Director?
Do you want to give up, just like that?
Ha, have I given up on Ban Joo-yeon?
It starts now
[Sound of pouring soju]
[Sound of putting down a bottle]
Ah, but isn’t that really too much?
(Edited) No, there was an accident or something.
Are you saying we should forget everything?
It's not just my fault
What accident?
I
I don't remember anything, I forgot everything
Ah, then why are you doing that?
What did I do?
You treat me like a thorn.
A thorn in my eye
The more you step on it, the more you step on it
That wriggling earthworm is me.
(Edited) The more I try to pull it out
I am the weed that takes root deeper
I lived like that for a while
If you try to break it, you stab it more.
So, whatever the former director says,
I'm just going to work hard like I always do.
I'll do the best I can
Of course, the head of the department might not like that.
You don’t like it?
[Exciting music]
Do you have a boss who doesn't like you working hard?
You didn’t like it?
A toxic bitch
The reason I don’t like being strong is because I’m weak.
(Juyeon) What I don’t like about being good at is
It's because I couldn't do it myself.
Of course
Of course it doesn't apply to me.
and
To be precise, I
It's not that I don't like it.
Because it's dangerous
[Slitting throat sound effect]
I want to remove it
[Exciting music]
(Edited) Yes?
Remove?
and!
Puuk
(Main role) Boom
[Bomb exploding sound effect]
Bam!
It's like a time bomb.
Are you just calling someone a bomb?
[groans with difficulty]
Boss!
Here are two more bottles of soju!
- (President) Yes, I understand.
- (Juyeon) Huh?
Can you do it?
[sigh]
(Shinwon) Wow, I feel refreshed
[Shinwon’s light sigh]
(Hajin) Next life is like clams
[lively music]
Born in the sea, I want to be immersed in alcohol.
It's a fun store
[Sujeong’s labored groans]
(Edited) What is it?
Ha, you're dead?
Director?
wake up
Yes?
Director...
go home and sleep
uncle
(Main role) Choco...
What?
(Main role) Chocolate milk
chocolate milk
[Baby laughing sound effect]
[lively music]
[Sujeong’s snort]
I heard you only drink espresso.
Drink chocolate milk at home.
(Edited) That general manager
What is your home address?
address
Sir, I would like to ask you to go to Yongseong Palace.
[tired elasticity]
[sigh]
(Wonseop) Now...
[sound of switch being turned off]
[Sound of lock locking]
(Edited) Dad
(Wonseop) Uh, daughter
Hey, are you leaving work now, huh?
Are you working overtime again?
Company dinner, why is Dad getting home from work now?
Uh, I'm not home from work yet.
Because there is a toilet leak in that 8 complex
I have to go look at that.
At this time?
(Wonseop) Oh, the owner of that house
They say the only time is now
(Edited) What is it, in what house?
Are you treating my dad like this?
(Wonseop) Hey, it’s okay to manipulate someone
Who's pampering me, huh?
I said I was going
You should earn it diligently while you can.
Later when I got old
What if the hospital bills end up being high?
[Calm music]
Ah, I was young when Mom got sick.
Now I have a daughter who makes good money.
You don't worry about anything
Work hard, think about your age
(Wonseop) Hey, your dad is young, he’s lively.
[Wonseop’s laughter]
[sniffing sound]
(Edited) Ah, where does the smell of paste come from, hmm.
Oh my
[sniffing sound]
Then you smell like alcohol
How much did you drink?
(Edited) By the way, if you do some outside work,
Maybe I could drink some
Making money isn't easy
[Wonseop’s laughter]
(Wonseop) That’s right
(Sujeong) I should have bought something for my dad too
(Wonseop) No
I just want to have a cold beer
(Edited) Then cancel it, 8th complex.
[Wonseop and Sujeong’s laughter]
(Wonseop) Is that so?
[Wonseop’s laughter]
[snoring sound]
[surprised moan]
[light music]
(Main role) Chocolate milk
chocolate milk
[Embarrassed groan]
[Exciting music]
(Juyeon) That’s ridiculous.
I...
I lost?
Baek Soo-jeong
In the end, I broke my social persona.
[Angrily moaning]
I can never forgive you
[Angrily breathing]
[bird chirping]
[Hyoseon’s groans of effort]
(Hyoseon) Renewal Project
You decided to proceed?
yes
Current department store sales
The reason it's standing still
Because there is no influx of new customers
(Juyeon) Likes new places
To our customers
Currently, Yongseong’s old image is poisonous.
Through store renewal
We will accelerate the influx of customers
(Hyoseon) It’s going to be a pretty big project.
It costs a lot of money
sometimes for growth
I think bold investment is needed.
Also from a long-term perspective.
[Sound of documents being closed]
I hope you don't have to be disappointed
Like before?
[dark music]
(Young Juyeon) Grandmother
Grandma don't do that
Grandma, grandma!
Never again...
You won't be disappointed
(In-kyung) You went home safely yesterday, right?
(Juyeon) Yes, of course
(In-kyung) As expected
There is no way to get drunk in any position.
There are no mistakes, so there is nothing to fix.
This is because you look just like the Chairman.
Just leave it like this
The Chairman will recognize it soon.
There is no successor like the general manager.
Because I think so too
(Juyeon) I want to get rid of it.
[Exciting music]
(Edit) Remove?
(Juyeon) Puuk, boom, paam!
It's like a time bomb.
[Sigh of Sujeong]
(Junsu) Hello?
How do you not have a hangover at all?
Even though we left yesterday
You ate a lot more, right?
Wow, I’m really jealous.
This crazy ability to break down alcohol is real.
how did i get here
Do you think you could have come up?
(Sujeong) It’s because everything has gone.
A brilliant mind is the base
(Junsu) Oh, so with that ability
Higher-ups at every drinking party
Did you go around killing everyone?
I can't even stop it from dying on its own.
Then yesterday, Director Ban also
(Nana) Did you kill me?
ah! Oh, kinda!
(Junsu) Oh, why don’t you give it a try this time?
(Edited) I don’t know how to lose
(Nana) Wow, it’s cool
You're amazing, really.
(Junsu) Ha, it’s really crazy.
So this director also
In front of the team leader
Did you just use injections?
[dark music]
(Edited) Write, you were just falling asleep?
ah!
Since I was drunk, I asked for that chocolate milk...
Aren't you working?
(Juyeon) Aren’t these work hours?
Have you completed your portfolio analysis?
What is the project plan?
Ah, that was yesterday...
We will proceed as quickly as possible
(Main role) Earthworms and weeds
How do you know you survived?
It's because humans watched.
If you step on an earthworm, it dies.
All you have to do is pull out the weeds.
Because it's annoying to get your hands and feet dirty
I saved it
Because you are doing well
Do you think I'm still here?
Please understand the topic
If you do not want to be collected separately
[nervous music]
[Sound of door opening]
(Nana) Team leader...
[Sound of door closing]
[sigh]
[Exciting music]
[Nana’s embarrassed groan]
Team leader?
[Sound of door opening]
(Edited) Hey!
Is it all about being the head of the headquarters?
Are you crazy?
How dare you tell me where this is...
(Edited) Dare?
How dare you
Do you ignore and insult people?
When you go out, you or I
It's the same person, people!
(Main role) Baek Soo-jeong, team leader
Why, Ban Joo-yeon?
(Edited) Outside the company
Let's take the title and stick with it, okay?
Let's start with the resignation letter.
(Juyeon) Are you saying we should remove the title?
Didn’t you say that with that much determination?
Would you like me to cut it for you?
[mumbling sound]
Yes!
Cut it! Cut it!
- (Edited) Yes? What's so difficult about that?
- (Junsu) Sorry, sorry!
[Exciting music]
Sorry, sorry, sorry, oh my, this
This is alcohol, alcohol
[The crystal resists]
I'll take you with me
- (Edited) I am resigning!
- (Junsu) You’re drinking too much right now.
No, no, no
- (Edited) I can resign right now.
- (Junsu) I’m sorry.
[Juyeon sighs]
[Sound of door closing]
[Inkyung’s sigh]
(In-kyung) If you do something like this,
I have no choice but to go out on my own.
If you do more
[Meaningful music]
The head of the department reported harassment or abuse of power in the workplace...
(Juyeon) I know, me too
It was too much
[sigh]
[Sound of opening a bottle cap]
(Junsu) Here
[Sujeong’s exasperated sigh]
[Junsu’s sigh]
(Junsu) It was a situation that made you angry.
[Indignant elasticity]
I'm just getting pissed too, right?
- But
- (Edited) Right, it was too much, right?
Ugh, I admit I acted like a crazy bitch.
No matter what they say, I should have endured it.
Ah, but I can’t stand it, what should I do!
If you are a superior, you can say anything.
Can I act like I want?
If you're a subordinate, you can't say anything?
That's not it, yeah
Ah, working to make a living is
It's the same salary, Mr.
Oh, that's not it either.
How did the general manager
Are you on the same salary as us?
(Edited) What is it, then?
Do you get paid an hourly wage other than a salary?
Is there a joke in this situation?
[sigh]
Are you really like this because you don’t know?
[light sigh]
(Junsu) No, from day one
There were rumors all over the place.
The rumor is true
Rumors?
Chairman's one and only
There is a rumor that it is his grandson.
(Junsu) Not a salaried worker, but a 3rd generation chaebol
Yongseong’s successor, Director Ban.
Ah!
[Interesting music]
Are you sure?
Yes, Director Kwon In-kyung, who goes with me, also
He was originally the chairman's direct secretary.
[surprised gasp]
(Junsu) Ah, I thought you knew roughly, but really.
Somehow
He was like a conglomerate.
[laughter]
(Edited) Well, I have the same abilities as myself.
I thought you became the head of the division at a young age.
Am I really going to get fired then?
(Junsu) Now, now, now!
Okay, so
Go and pray right now
If you ask me well, you'll see it, right?
Oh, I'm really with the team leader.
I want to keep working
Team leader
- Oh, team leader, what are you thinking now?
- (Edited) That...
How to make it uncut
Yes?
[Flashing sound effect]
A chaebol that is not dirty among chaebols
I didn't see it, I
(Shinwon) Ah
The story about Team Leader Baek Soo-jeong
I collected them all
(Employee) It's a bit scary when you're an enemy from the moment you join the company.
[Interesting music]
I felt reassured when we were on the same side.
Anyway, a bit tired?
Are you the team leader?
He's absolutely my role model.
It's a little... difficult.
I'm having a bit of a hard time
But he's a really cool guy, really.
(Shinwon) Just work hard
Looks like a person?
If I had to say a disadvantage,
The energy is too strong, the work is crazy, it’s terrible.
So I think it would suit you well.
What is it?
- (Juyeon) What?
- (Identity) Why?
Because you finally became interested in a girl
Didn't I tell you to investigate?
My brother first agrees.
After you got dumped by your first love
You haven't met anyone
How long will this last?
Good idea, let's get over it now, okay?
[Sound of hitting table]
[Sharp sound effect]
(Juyeon) One more time in front of me
You said you'd never see me again if I brought this up, right?
Isn't this it?
No, but why are you investigating Team Leader Baek?
That's it, I don't need it anymore
Because it's all over
[Mouse operation sound]
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
[Spooky music]
[nervous music]
[ID tag sound]
[sigh]
[Humorous sound effects]
[humorous music]
Take just one, just one
(Edited) Commoner cosplay, what is it?
Ah...
When will it come out?
fashion real
Ah, but where on earth are you going, ah...
[Noisy noise]
(Juyeon) Be careful
[Exciting music]
[Microphone beeps]
[People cheering]
[Sigh of relief]
[rock and roll singing voice]
(Singer) Everyone run together!
[rock and roll music playing]
[rock and roll singing voice]
[Cheers from the main cast]
It’s completely different from work.
(Edited) Wow, I really don’t recognize you.
Huh?
This is perfect
Instead, forget about Team Leader Baek Soo-jeong.
[lively music]
you and me
We've never met outside of work.
Double life?
yes
Because there’s something poking at the map.
I guess you said let’s forget everything.
It's a judgment call, Mr.
[Doorbell sounds]
[Sound of door opening]
Ah, who is it at this time, Mr. Lee?
[Doorbell sounds]
(Edited) Who is it?
(Wonseop) Oh, I don’t know.
[Juyeon’s heavy breathing]
[Exciting music]
[Wonseop’s embarrassed groan]
Who are you?
Soo-jeong Baek?
Let me see for a second.
(Wonseop) Have you got a boyfriend?
Oh, don't say anything
Oh, don't open it!
[Wallpad button sound]
[Door lock operating sound]
[Sound of door opening]
Let's talk, we
[Humorous sound effects]
[Juyeon’s nervous breathing]
(Edited) What is it, on this night?
Why did you come to this place?
You want to talk?
What are you talking about bare-mouthed?
(Sujeong) Convenient and delicious nearby
I came to a clean place.
What about business?
My plan for Baek Soo-jeong
I decided to change it
(Juyeon) Now Baek Soo-jeong
not subject to removal
Subject to close monitoring and protection
[Interesting music]
Yes?
(Edited) This...
Soo-jeong Baek
Ban Joo-yeon's photo will be deleted immediately.
(Juyeon) Ban Juyeon’s private life
everything related to
External disclosure is prohibited.
Baek Soo-jeong immediately responds to Ban Joo-yeon's call.
As long as Baeksujeong fulfills the terms of the contract
Ban Joo-yeon ensures Baek Soo-jeong's employment stability.
Absolutely guaranteed
Are you serious?
What we both want is clear
Don't waste time
(Juyeon) Please sign
[Signs with a pen]
[Growling sound effect]
I said the name was nasty right from the start.
(Edited) I think the name is just ordinary.
What do you mean?
I heard the name is nasty right?
What's wrong with your name?
[absurd gasping sound]
Why don’t you just delete the photo?
Now you really can't cut me
Why do you like dragons so much?
Didn’t it hurt when you got the dragon tattoo?
It's henna, not a tattoo.
[Humorous sound effects]
Ah...
[lively music]
[light laughter]
(Edited) Hello, good morning.
Good morning!
Good morning
(Nana) Team leader
You look in a good mood today?
Does it show a lot?
(Edited) Nana
Do you know what is most important to office workers?
vacation, salary
All are correct, but the basic thing is job security.
(Edited) Good morning, Director.
[light laughter]
yes, good morning
[Devil's Laughing Sound Effect]
Are you accepting my greeting?
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
(Seokhee) Enjoy your meal
- (Nana) Enjoy your meal.
- (Junsu) Enjoy your meal
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[upbeat music]
(Edited) Oh, please take this away for me.
I'm sorry
[cell phone vibrating sound]
IC
[Messenger notification sound]
(Juyeon) To the general manager’s office
[Crystal Lament]
This...
If you read it all...
(Juyeon) Do not read and destroy.
there
Why?
After job security is guaranteed
Don't you want to work?
no matter what i do
He said he would work hard
[Shredder operating sound]
Well, isn’t it noisy?
(Edited) Ah, why here?
There are shredders outside.
Well, can I go out?
yes?
[Humorous sound effects]
What did you say?
Ah...
It must not have been noisy
(Edited) That, perhaps
Are you taking revenge on me?
It's surveillance.
When you reveal top secret information and threaten someone
I should have made this much preparation.
Oh, by the way
With that picture
Why is it all top secret?
(Sujeong) Ah, I thought you wanted to hide something.
I sent it
I didn't know that would work.
Did you forget?
who am i
Yongseong successor or something?
Isn’t the successor even a person?
[Calm music]
(Edited) Ah, my personal fashion taste sucks.
Looks like he's enjoying the performance
Ah, that might be a bit extreme.
Are you insulting me now?
Are you being patronizing?
Anyway
Like other chaebols
It's not even a private life that would appear in the news.
What are you hiding so much?
For Yongseong’s successor, who must be perfect
It's also unnecessary privacy.
Why do you do that when you work?
You often hear people ask if you are doing it terribly, right?
Why do you do that?
Because I lived like that
This is how I live
my answer is the same
This is my way, so
Stop wasting time and finish working.
[Sigh of Sujeong]
[Shredder operating sound]
I'm finally home from work
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Sigh of Sujeong]
(Hajin) Sujeong-ah, that photo I mentioned last time.
Can you send it to me now?
picture?
[The surprising elasticity of crystals]
[humorous music]
Why are you looking at other people's cell phones?
(Juyeon) Have you forgotten that you are subject to close surveillance?
Anyway, if you use someone else's cell phone
It's a food photo, a food photo.
(Edited) This girl owns the store.
Because I’m not talking about the photo of the head of the department.
don't worry
Oh, it's real.
Anyway, I did everything you asked me to do.
I'm going to leave work now
I can't
How can I trust Baek Soo-jeong?
Well then, stick around all day
Would you like to keep an eye on me?
yes
- yes?
- Follow me.
[absurd elasticity]
[Elegant music plays]
(Edited) I’ll stick with this.
Why does Baek Soo-jeong choose the clothes she wears?
lovers in paris
Ah, I thought I'd do that again
I'm buying my own clothes
Not that one, this one
Then why did you bring me here?
(Edited) Yes?
madam...
[Music: ‘That Guy is the Black Flame Dragon’ OST]
It's not that good
[Satisfied moan]
again
[laughter]
Turn around again, yes.
yes
Well...
(Juyeon) Please change your clothes and come out.
Because I can’t go like that.
Oh, where are you going again?
(Edited) Oh, and this
It’s not even my style?
I'm not interested in that style.
Come out wearing it
(Edited) Mr...
[Card payment sound]
[Music: ‘That Guy is the Black Flame Dragon’ OST]
Oh, look, it's not my style.
It doesn't suit you, does it?
It doesn't suit me
[absurd elasticity]
I lent it to you, so please return it by tomorrow.
I'm going to return it now, so please take me home from work, right?
I refuse
(Edited) Lady...
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
[Door bell sounds]
(Shinwon) Write, I think it’s here.
(Hajin) Surely you are a guest?
Are you coming to the store?
Oh, are you the boss?
Did you open the door?
Sure, go in.
(Shinwon) Ah, yes
[Hajin’s surprised exclamation]
[nervous music]
[Paper flutters]
[Sparkling sound effect]
[Exciting music]
(Hajin) Are you okay?
customer?
[Sparkling sound effect]
[ding sound effect]
[Shinwon’s embarrassed exclamation]
(Hajin) My back muscles
Oh, are you okay with that?
Ah, well, as you can see I
(Hajin) Anyway, I’m out of my mind.
Please go in first
I'll put this away and go right in.
(Shinwon) Oh, I’ll help you too.
(Hajin) No, it’s okay
(Shinwon) It’s okay, me too
(Eunhee) Oppa
What are you doing?
(Shinwon) Uh...
(Hajin) The food you ordered has arrived.
(ID) Thank you
brother
Are you hungry? Let's eat quickly
I've been thinking about it
Yeah, what were you thinking?
I don't know if he really likes me
(Shinwon) How do you not know that?
How pretty and how much I like you
(Eunhee) Oppa does this to everyone.
Be nice, kind, and smile
But you're my only girlfriend?
So what are you doing?
It's the same now as it was before we started dating.
Do you think so?
[sigh]
we break up
[Sound of putting down chopsticks]
- Eunhee.
- (Eunhee) I liked it better before I started dating my oppa.
I'm so anxious now
It's miserable
(Shinwon) Um...
Okay then
Let's break up
What?
Right like this?
I'd rather you be miserable
Because I want you to be happy
[laughter]
(Eunhee) Wow...
You really are a bad bastard
[Eunhee’s sigh]
[Sound of door opening]
[Door bell sounds]
[Sound of door closing]
Would you like it?
To this bad boy
Wouldn’t you like to sell raw fish?
Did you cheat?
Oh, no way
Then he's not that bad.
He was just a good person to everyone.
But people
They called it a flirt
You have to cheat to be a cheater.
That's right
(Hajin) came out
(Shinwon) Hey, the raw fish was aged well.
The thickness is appropriate
Oh, thank goodness.
Oh, could you please give me a bottle of soju?
[Exciting music plays]
[People’s excited exclamations]
[Sound of clinking glasses]
(Juyeon) [Laughing] That’s vulgar.
(Edited) Why on earth did you come here?
(Juyeon) I’m here to meet an important customer.
(Edited) Ah, just to reassure you, Director.
I did come
Don't think about introducing me as your girlfriend.
I got strangely entangled with a chaebol.
Because I don't want to do that
(Main lead) Baek Soo-jeong?
(Edited) Yes?
Who do you think would be more reluctant to get involved?
(Juyeon) When on earth was Cinderella Storage?
I've been feeling like an old person since a while ago
It's not like I'm showing off
Yes, it would be nice to be young.
Not really, it's unpleasant
(Chaebol Man 1) Huh? Hey, isn’t he the lead actor?
(Chaebol Man 2) Yongseong's supporting role?
(Chaebol Man 1) Huh? Is it true?
Why did he come here?
-Why are they idiots like that?
- (Chaebol Man 2) Ban Ju-yeon, what are you?
(Chaebol Man 1) Are you alive?
Wait here, don't move.
Yes? Wait...
Ah, how long...
Oh, that idiot, really.
I think I'm going to run away, Mr.
[Stomach growling sound]
(Edit) Ah, I’m hungry.
(Chaebol Man 1) Hey, Ban Ju-yeon
Weren't you in America?
When did you come to Korea?
(Chaebol Man 2) This time, the department store
Looks like the rumor that he was appointed is true.
Awesome
(Chaebol Man 1) Hey, I’m your grandmother.
I thought you abandoned me, man.
They won't give me a position at the company
(Chaebol Man 2) Hey, don’t say anything that will cause trouble.
Jooyeon hasn’t even received the stock gift yet.
If I'm abandoned like this, it's a duck egg from the Namhan River.
[Chaebol Man 2’s laughter]
[snort]
Whenever I see you, you are always as fun as ever.
(Chaebol Man 1) We always have fun living
Hey, you too, have some fun, man.
Listening to grandma
Don't live without doing anything
Well, I'm enjoying it quite a bit too.
I feel like I'm living
(Chaebol Man 2) What do you say?
You don't drink, you don't gamble in America
You've been living a crazy life
You came alone today too, right?
Hey, take it.
Find a boy with a good body quickly and come here.
(Woman) A good-looking guy?
Is that so?
I decline.
(Chaebol Man 2) Oh, you boring bastard, are you leaving me out again?
(Main role) Alcohol, women, gambling
What you think is fun
It's so obvious it's pathetic
Looks like a rag
[nervous music]
What?
What did you just say?
Did I say she was a slut?
(Juyeon) You to me
It's always fun to tease
I guess it's an intelligence issue, right?
I don’t even know about Nakdong River duck eggs.
It is called the Namhangang River.
[snort]
[Exciting music plays]
[Chaebol Man 3 clears his throat]
(Chaebol Man 3) This is my first time seeing your face.
You know me, right?
what? Are you a chaebol too?
(Chaebol Man 3) Yes, that’s right, Chaebol
If you came alone, would you play with me?
[snort]
Then I take their stuff or whatever.
It must be a customer, so why are you speaking so briefly?
(Edited) Be polite to customers
Isn’t that what you make a living at? If you’re a chaebol?
[Chaebol Man 3’s laughter]
(Chaebol Man 3) Oh, this bitch is funny?
Write, no, from when I saw you earlier.
Just look at our people
I thought it wasn't so
You were a customer.
Huh?
Okay
I'll treat you like a queen
in bed
[nervous music]
Hey, let go
- (Edit) Don’t let it go?
- I liked the angry concept.
(Chaebol Man 3) Do you see one or two things like this?
Stop it and go
[Chaebol Man 3 groans in pain]
[mumbling sound]
Is this really crazy?
[laughter]
[Soft music]
Baby, let's go
[Music: ‘That Guy is the Black Flame Dragon’ OST]
[Music: ‘He’s a Black Flame Dragon’ OST-continued]
(Main role) Baek Soo-jeong, surveillance level declines
Just keep your clothes.
Because I didn’t really need it and I was pretty.
(Nana) former team leader
I thought you disliked the manager.
(Edit) Ah, where are the likes and dislikes?
Just do a good job
(Shinwon) Is there really such a thing as destiny?
(Edited) So please feel free to like it.
(Juyeon) Let’s like it more to our heart’s content.
in front of you
(Hajin) I received a gift for opening the business.
(Edited) Who is sending a gift like this?
Black flame dragon?